hi everyone sri lanka welcome back to my
channel guys adam verwell and if it's
your first time you know what to do
please consider subscribing below i'll
do my best to keep you informed
entertain inspired and intrigued with
all my youtube videos and as you can see
the title of this particular video of
course
we'll be reacting to another blind of
additions for your the voice
and uh for this video we'll be watching
um chathoria sandara
sunda
let me know what the title of this song
is you know the definition of it guys
okay let me know below in the comments
and of course i'm quite excited to watch
another round of editions
and also i will be linking this video on
the description box
so that um you can watch it for yourself
later on but if you
if you're a fan of you know the voice of
course
most probably you have watched it
already alright
here we go
okay there she is
you know what it started quite uh unique
for me because the beat
actually is quite a fast
something to do with the drums and of
course the words uh even though i don't
understand it seems as if it's
has this um melody
is you know quite uh catchy uh so far
let's check further
[Music]
i don't know if i have like
watch someone performed this song before
yeah because it does sound familiar to
me that's why the reason why i mentioned
earlier that the
beat or the melody is quite memorable
um if you already know i have
reviewed a lot of the voice teens sri
lanka
a couple of months ago so i believe
there is some possibility
that of course for the addition for the
current the voice
the song would repeat if you know what i
[Music]
mean
i love the control of her voice and also
the tonality on it
absolutely awesome
[Music]
yeah you know what this part uh right
here i always
get sort of the same at technique or
vocal placement
of especially from sri lankan
the voice also with the teens
um i don't know it could be on the mix
register or on the chesty mix
that's my observation all throughout to
be
[Music]
to be honest you know scratch my opinion
earlier i believe it's more on the head
didn't mix tone
it's more in the falsetto already
[Music]
that part right there yeah
but by the way i have to point out her
ponytail i'm getting ariana grande vibes
really really beautiful
[Music]
you know what like there's a lot of mini
riffs and runs that you can
almost hear but really really subtle and
it takes a lot of technique and you know
what
also her i can
tell that she's actually quite young
so i think for the regular season of the
voice which is the one that we're
watching right now it could be like 18
years
up for however for the voice teams it
should be i think
i believe 18 years uh you know younger
or you know below
but a pen like looking at the thumbnail
you know and watching her it seems as
though she's actually quite young
so i don't know about that
oh we have three chairs already
and she's quite glad about that as
she should
[Music]
yeah while i appreciate the this
control of her head voice
i was you know i'm actually still
waiting for her to
i don't know maybe sing on her natural
voice you know the chess voice but so
far it has been quite
awesome
[Music]
and you know what it goes up and down
goes up and down
wow that last bit
that last part right there let's try to
you know repeat that again
she's gorgeous by the way look at that
look at her
let's try to repeat that last part okay
our voice
yeah you know i've always
find it quite unique that singing style
that part right there you guys
that was a good addition for chathuria
santa barbara
yeah she's really really beautiful and
i don't know who is the coach she will
be choosing
up until now there's still no english
subtitles for you know the voice sri
lanka i believe
they they would not like really add
anytime
soon but i do wish that maybe in the
future or
for this season perhaps i don't know
music yeah that's what i understand so
far but anyway that was a stellar
edition for chathuryah cinder bharana
singing hithala
like i said though i was just maybe
waiting for the song to
take off into a much powerful climax i
guess but
i you know i believe that was just how
it
maybe the song has limitations it was
just
meant to be sung that way you know what
i mean
anyway i'll see in my next upload guys
let me know below in the comments
uh what or whose blind edition should we
react review and analyze snacks okay bye